# Guilherme Patriota

#### Database Administrator



APT 1001-6800 Chemin de la Côte-St-Luc Montréal/QC



+1 (438) 926-0872



linkedin.com/in/guilhermepatriota



quipatriota@gmail.com

## About me —

Guilherme Patriota is a fast learner professional who works as IT/database Professor and Electrical Engineer with a Masters in AI in search of an opportunity to work in his areas of interest. Working as a University Professor in the Computer Engineering and Data Science courses since 2016 I know I can make the difference at your company to achieve financial goals and make the crypto world a trusted place to trade money again.

# Skills

Team Work, Analytical Mind, Teaching

AWS, RDS, Linux Shell, Docker

Eletronics, IoT, MQTT, Kafka

Hbase, Redis, MongoDB, Elasticsearch

Python, AI, Logic, C++, R, Skala

DBA, SQL DDL, MySQL, NoSQL

Big Data, Hadoop, Spark

(\*)[The skill scale is from 0 (Fundamental Awareness) to 6 (Expert).]

#### Interests

Cryptocurrencies; Database Administration and security; Big Data

## Education

2013-2016	MBA in Healthcare	FGV/Brazil
	Improuvments into medical equipments maintenance.	
2009-2011	M.Sc. Electrical Engineer  AI with electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2002-2006	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer Electronics and telecommunications.	UFPR/Brazil
2004-2004	B.Sc. Electrical Engineer	ENSPS/France

Sandwitch degree in Electrical Engineer - Electronics

#### Complementary Studies

2020	Knowledge discovery in database and datamining. UFPR/Brazil	60h
2020	Data Science foundations.  Aldeia Coworking/Brazil	32h
2020	Introduction to computer programming using python. MITx	9 weeks
2020	AI fundamentals.  Data Science Academy	8h
2020	Datascience 2.0. Data Science Academy	8h

## Experience

since 2016

	ing and Data Science courses at UNINTER - Internation Center in Brasil and Educator at AWS Academy.	onal University
2020-2021	New Technologies Developer  Develop eletronics and software for new 3d printers and ucts. Manage projects database. Manage the assembly	•
2018-2020	3D Printer Engineer.  Build, repair end configure 3d printer and 3d modeling.	GS3D

University Professor in the Software Engineering, Computer Engineer-

**FAESP and UNINTER** 

# 2012-2018 Clinical Engineer. Several Hospitals in Brazil Maintain and repair medical and non medical equipments. Manage Datacenter. Mantain hospiatl and pacients database secure and online 24/7. Manage technician and IT teams.

## Other information

Disponibility

OWP for Part and full time.

Languages

Fluency in English, French and Portuguese.

University Professor

Social

GitHub github.com/guipatriota

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/guilhermepatriota